let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "What does h mean in HTMl?",
        answer: "A. heading",
        options: [
            "A. heading",
            "B. title",
            "C. sheet",
            "D. Home"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Who is the head of Nigeria",
        answer: "C. Tinubu Bola Ahmed",
        options: [
            "A. Tinubu Adebola",
            "B. Ahmed Taye",
            "C. Tinubu Bola Ahmed",
            "D. Funmi Adebola"
            ]
    },

    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "what is the odd one out of the options?",
        answer: "B. Farming",
        options: [
            "A. HTML",
            "B. Farming",
            "C. CSS",
            "D. Javascript"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "What is the full meaning of Maths",
        answer: "A. Mathematics",
        options: [
            "A. Mathematics",
            "B. English",
            "C. Statitics",
            "D. Christain Religious"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "What is the second name of Jasmine",
        answer: "D. Omolara",
        options: [
            "A. Adebola",
            "B. Chrissy",
            "C. Violet",
            "D. Omolara"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "which heading have the largest font size",
        answer: "B. h1",
        options: [
            "A. h3",
            "B. h1",
            "C. h4",
            "D. h5"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "what does CSS stands for?",
        answer: "B. Cascading Stylesheet",
        options: [
            "A. Christy stylesite",
            "B. Cascading Stylesheet",
            "C. Cascading Styleplus",
            "D. Christy Stylesheet"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "which is the odd one out?",
        answer: "A. HTML",
        options: [
            "A. HTML",
            "B. Java",
            "C. Python",
            "D. Javascript"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Which of these delicacy belongs to Nigeria",
        answer: "C. Pounded yam",
        options: [
            "A. Pizza",
            "B. Pasta",
            "C. Pounded yam",
            "D. Chicken nuggets"

        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "C in CSS stands for 'Cascading'",
        answer: "A. True",
        options: [
            "A. True",
            "B. false"
        ]
    },
];